One sort of vowel used in colloquial Tamil that is not found in English, though familiar to speakers of say French, is nasal vowels.
Practice these sounds by repeating the words that follow. The English meaning is given first.
May come.
வரலாம் (varalaam)
He came.
வந்தான் (vandaan)
Tree.
மரம் (maram)
We came.
வந்தோம் (vandoom)
He.
அவன் (avan)
I came.
வந்தேன் (vandeen)
It will come.
வரும் (varum)
If these words are made into questions by the addition of the sound 'aa', the vowels are no longer nasal. Instead, an 'm' or an 'n' as indicated in the written form is pronounced before the following vowel.
Try the same words as questions by repeating the following.
வரலாமா
வந்தானா
மரமா
வந்தோமா
அவனா
வந்தேனா
வருமா